{"data":[{"question":"Earlier or later, all lakes are influenced by eutrophication, a process in which lake  sediment lowers the depth of the water and drains oxygen from it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Earlier ","b":"influenced by ","c":"the depth ","d":"from it","answer":"1","explain":"- Earlier or later-> sooner or later","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Jekyll island has been one of Georgia's State parks in 1954.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"one ","b":"State ","c":"parks ","d":"in ","answer":"4","explain":"- In-> since","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Bells are frequently made from bronze, an alloy of approximately three part copper  and one part tin.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"made from ","b":"an alloy ","c":"approximately","d":"part copper  ","answer":"4","explain":"- Part cooper-> parts cooper","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Negotiable instruments such as personal checks may ordinarily be transferred to another people by endorsement.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Negotiable ","b":"ordinarily ","c":"people ","d":"by endorsement","answer":"3","explain":"- People-> person","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Scientists and economists believe that human beings can never use away all the  mineral resources on Earth.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"believe ","b":"can never ","c":"use away ","d":"mineral ","answer":"3","explain":"- Use away-> use up","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Idaho ranks first among the states in potatoes production.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"ranks ","b":"among ","c":"in ","d":"potatoes ","answer":"4","explain":"- Potatoes->potatoe","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"The decay of a muon is an example of an weak interaction between atomic particles.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"decay ","b":"an example ","c":"an weak ","d":"atomic particles","answer":"3","explain":"- A weak-> a weak","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"All village or tribe of the North American Indian confederacy had its annual green   corn dance, a festival in which social ties were renewed.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"All ","b":"annual ","c":"a festival ","d":"social ","answer":"1","explain":"- All-> each\/a","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Pipelines are continually inspected for leaks and for damage caused by such  conditions as freezing temperatures, heavy rain, and soil erode. \n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"for damage ","b":"freezing temperatures","c":"heavy rain","d":"soil erode","answer":"4","explain":"- Soil erode-> soil erosion","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Plastics used to make textiles can be drawn into fine threads, then woven or knit into fabrics.                                           \n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"can be drawn ","b":"fine threads","c":"woven ","d":"knit    ","answer":"4","explain":"- Knit-> knitted","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"}]}